const quizArr = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the significance of Eid al-Fitr?",
    options: {
      A: "Celebration of the end of Ramadan",
      B: "Commemoration of the Prophet's birthday",
      C: "Celebration of the Hajj pilgrimage",
      D: "Marking the beginning of Ramadan",
    },
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What is the traditional dish often eaten during Eid al-Fitr?",
    options: {
      A: "Biryani",
      B: "Samosa",
      C: "Kheer",
      D: "Pasta",
    },
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What is the name of the prayer performed on Eid?",
    options: {
      A: "Dhuhr",
      B: "Fajr",
      C: "Eid Salah",
      D: "Asr",
    },
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What is given to the poor before the Eid al-Fitr prayer?",
    options: {
      A: "Zakat al-Fitr",
      B: "Sadaqah",
      C: "Khums",
      D: "Fidyah",
    },
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Which month does Eid al-Fitr fall in?",
    options: {
      A: "Shawwal",
      B: "Ramadan",
      C: "Dhu al-Hijjah",
      D: "Muharram",
    },
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What is a common greeting exchanged during Eid?",
    options: {
      A: "Merry Christmas",
      B: "Happy New Year",
      C: "Eid Mubarak",
      D: "Happy Diwali",
    },
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What is the name of the festival that celebrates the willingness of Ibrahim to sacrifice his son?",
    options: {
      A: "Eid al-Fitr",
      B: "Eid al-Adha",
      C: "Mawlid",
      D: "Laylat al-Miraj",
    },
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is the customary practice after the Eid prayer?",
    options: {
      A: "Fasting",
      B: "Feasting",
      C: "Mourning",
      D: "Traveling",
    },
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Which animal is commonly sacrificed during Eid al-Adha?",
    options: {
      A: "Cow",
      B: "Goat",
      C: "Sheep",
      D: "All of the above",
    },
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What is the purpose of wearing new clothes on Eid?",
    options: {
      A: "To show off wealth",
      B: "To celebrate the occasion",
      C: "To impress others",
      D: "To follow tradition",
    },
    answer: "B",
  },
];